<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; Cerca la copertura</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 21:19:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/cropped-2024-01-28-03_06_28-logo-quadrato-en-1.png-473×374-Copy-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News &#8211; Cerca la copertura</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Inauguration of trade fair, increased entry fee</title>
		<link>/inauguration-of-trade-fair-increased-entry-fee/</link>
					<comments>/inauguration-of-trade-fair-increased-entry-fee/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 21:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10953</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina inaugurated the month-long 28th Dhaka International Trade Fair. The head of government inaugurated the fair at the Bangabandhu Bangladesh-China Friendship Exhibition Center in Purbachal New Town on the outskirts of the capital on Sunday morning. Close PlayerUnibots.in Ministry of Commerce and Export Promotion Bureau (EPB) jointly organized this fair. Read More ... <a title="Inauguration of trade fair, increased entry fee" class="read-more" href="/inauguration-of-trade-fair-increased-entry-fee/" aria-label="More on Inauguration of trade fair, increased entry fee">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina inaugurated the month-long 28th Dhaka International Trade Fair. The head of government inaugurated the fair at the Bangabandhu Bangladesh-China Friendship Exhibition Center in Purbachal New Town on the outskirts of the capital on Sunday morning. </p>
<p>Close PlayerUnibots.in<br />
Ministry of Commerce and Export Promotion Bureau (EPB) jointly organized this fair.</p>
<p>Read More >>   Farmgate Buses to Trade Fair, Know Fares<br />
Commerce State Minister Ahsanul Islam, Commerce Ministry Senior Secretary Tapan Kanti Ghosh, Federation of Bangladesh Chamber of Commerce and Industry (FBCCI) President Mahbubul Alam spoke on the occasion.</p>
<p>Export Promotion Bureau (EPB) vice chairman AHM Ahsan gave a welcome speech. A video documentary was screened on the occasion on the steps taken by the government in the last 15 years to develop and expand business and attract local and foreign investment.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/inauguration-of-trade-fair-increased-entry-fee/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The price of gold decreased in the world market</title>
		<link>/the-price-of-gold-decreased-in-the-world-market/</link>
					<comments>/the-price-of-gold-decreased-in-the-world-market/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 21:18:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10951</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Recently, a new history has been created in the gold price in the country&#8217;s market while the price of gold is falling in the world market. However, the day after the record price was set, gold prices were reduced. The case of reducing the price the day after the price increase has never happened in ... <a title="The price of gold decreased in the world market" class="read-more" href="/the-price-of-gold-decreased-in-the-world-market/" aria-label="More on The price of gold decreased in the world market">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recently, a new history has been created in the gold price in the country&#8217;s market while the price of gold is falling in the world market. However, the day after the record price was set, gold prices were reduced. The case of reducing the price the day after the price increase has never happened in the country before.</p>
<p>Last January 18, the price of the best quality or 22 carat gold was increased by 1 thousand 400 taka to 1 lakh 12 thousand 441 taka. The price of a 21 carat gold bar has been increased by Tk 1,283 to Tk 1,7,309.</p>
<p>Besides, the price of one 18 carat gold bar has been increased by 1 thousand 166 taka to 92 thousand 29 taka. And according to the traditional method, the price of one load of gold was increased by 933 taka to 76 thousand 632 taka. This is the highest price of gold in the market of the country. Gold was sold at this record price only on January 18.</p>
<p>The next day i.e. January 19, the price of the best quality or 22 carat gold was reduced by Tk 1,750 to Tk 1,10,691. The price of a 21 carat gold bar has been reduced from Tk 1,633 to Tk 1,5,676.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/the-price-of-gold-decreased-in-the-world-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Awami League has given the program on January 30</title>
		<link>/awami-league-has-given-the-program-on-january-30/</link>
					<comments>/awami-league-has-given-the-program-on-january-30/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 21:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10949</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The party&#8217;s general secretary and Road Transport and Bridges Minister Obaidul Quader announced the program from the peace and democracy rally organized by the Dhaka Metropolitan South Awami League in front of the party&#8217;s central office at Bangabandhu Avenue in the capital on Saturday (January 27) afternoon. Obaidul Quader said that China-India-Russia may be friends, ... <a title="Awami League has given the program on January 30" class="read-more" href="/awami-league-has-given-the-program-on-january-30/" aria-label="More on Awami League has given the program on January 30">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The party&#8217;s general secretary and Road Transport and Bridges Minister Obaidul Quader announced the program from the peace and democracy rally organized by the Dhaka Metropolitan South Awami League in front of the party&#8217;s central office at Bangabandhu Avenue in the capital on Saturday (January 27) afternoon.</p>
<p>Obaidul Quader said that China-India-Russia may be friends, but the government came to power by the people&#8217;s vote. Commodity prices will decrease soon, Sheikh Hasina has started working with the entire cabinet.</p>
<p>Earlier on Saturday (January 27) at noon, BNP announced this program from the black flag march demanding the release of party chairperson Khaleda Zia and the jailed leaders and activists, reducing the prices of daily commodities and canceling the illegal parliament. The party&#8217;s standing committee member Gayeshwar Chandra Roy announced the programme. Addressing the leaders and workers of the party, he said, we should not return home with satisfaction, we have to carry out the program on the streets.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/awami-league-has-given-the-program-on-january-30/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arrested when the accused came to the BNP procession</title>
		<link>/arrested-when-the-accused-came-to-the-bnp-procession/</link>
					<comments>/arrested-when-the-accused-came-to-the-bnp-procession/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 21:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10947</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[He said this in response to a question from journalists at the DMP media center on Saturday (January 27) at noon. Liton Kumar Saha said, &#8216;We are arresting the accused under the warrant. BNP has a program, we have extensive preparations to arrest any accused under warrant. No accused has come to the program but ... <a title="Arrested when the accused came to the BNP procession" class="read-more" href="/arrested-when-the-accused-came-to-the-bnp-procession/" aria-label="More on Arrested when the accused came to the BNP procession">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>He said this in response to a question from journalists at the DMP media center on Saturday (January 27) at noon.</p>
<p>Liton Kumar Saha said, &#8216;We are arresting the accused under the warrant. BNP has a program, we have extensive preparations to arrest any accused under warrant. No accused has come to the program but we haven&#8217;t caught it.&#8217;</p>
<p>In response to another question, he said, &#8216;Political parties are always carrying out their programs. We are not obstructing any political program.&#8217;</p>
<p>BNP has planned a black flag procession in Nayapaltan of the capital on Saturday. The party is carrying out this program to protest against the increase in commodity prices, release of all royal prisoners including party chairperson Khaleda Zia, withdrawal of cases and cancellation of &#8216;illegal parliament&#8217;.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/arrested-when-the-accused-came-to-the-bnp-procession/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mother hanged after killing two children</title>
		<link>/mother-hanged-after-killing-two-children/</link>
					<comments>/mother-hanged-after-killing-two-children/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 21:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10945</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A mother committed suicide after killing her two children. The incident took place in Kamalpur village of Gutudia Union No. 13 of Dumuria Upazila of Khulna on Saturday (January 27) morning. Close PlayerUnibots.in The deceased are Dolly Begum (38), wife of Mannan Sardar of Kamalpur village in the upazila, and her daughter Fatema (6) and ... <a title="Mother hanged after killing two children" class="read-more" href="/mother-hanged-after-killing-two-children/" aria-label="More on Mother hanged after killing two children">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A mother committed suicide after killing her two children. The incident took place in Kamalpur village of Gutudia Union No. 13 of Dumuria Upazila of Khulna on Saturday (January 27) morning. </p>
<p>Close PlayerUnibots.in<br />
The deceased are Dolly Begum (38), wife of Mannan Sardar of Kamalpur village in the upazila, and her daughter Fatema (6) and 7-month-old son Omar. </p>
<p>Police and locals said that between 8 am and 11 pm on Saturday, Dolly Begum killed her two children and committed suicide by hanging herself due to a family dispute at her home.</p>
<p>Officer-in-Charge (OC) of Dumuria Police Station Sukant Saha said that the details of the incident are yet to be known. The process of recovering the body and sending it for post-mortem is underway.</p>
<p>Khulna Additional Superintendent of Police. Asif Iqbal told the media that the police recovered the bodies of three people. Mother committed suicide by hanging herself. Two more children were found dead. The house was blocked. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/mother-hanged-after-killing-two-children/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Border guards are on alert at the Myanmar border</title>
		<link>/border-guards-are-on-alert-at-the-myanmar-border/</link>
					<comments>/border-guards-are-on-alert-at-the-myanmar-border/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 21:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10943</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[He said these things after a courtesy meeting with a delegation of four members of the British Parliament at the Rashtriya Guest House Padma on Saturday (January 27) at 1 pm. Dr. Hasan Mahmud said that discussions were held with four members of the British Parliament regarding Myanmar. The tense situation in Myanmar&#8217;s Rakhine state ... <a title="Border guards are on alert at the Myanmar border" class="read-more" href="/border-guards-are-on-alert-at-the-myanmar-border/" aria-label="More on Border guards are on alert at the Myanmar border">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>He said these things after a courtesy meeting with a delegation of four members of the British Parliament at the Rashtriya Guest House Padma on Saturday (January 27) at 1 pm.</p>
<p>Dr. Hasan Mahmud said that discussions were held with four members of the British Parliament regarding Myanmar. The tense situation in Myanmar&#8217;s Rakhine state did not happen suddenly. It&#8217;s been a few more days. Our border guards have been on alert there for a long time. A tense situation arose there after a few days. We have always sought the help of the international community. They are with us. If the international community puts pressure on Myanmar, they will be forced to take back their citizens (Rohingya).</p>
<p>He further said that the border guards of Bangladesh are on alert as the situation in Myanmar&#8217;s Rakhine state is once again tense.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/border-guards-are-on-alert-at-the-myanmar-border/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kuwait bans handshakes</title>
		<link>/kuwait-bans-handshakes/</link>
					<comments>/kuwait-bans-handshakes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 21:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10941</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Kuwait&#8217;s Ministry of Health has called on mourners gathered at cemeteries to give up handshakes and make eye contact to show their condolences, al-Zarida reported, citing an official. Saud Al Dabus, director-general of Kuwait Municipality, said a circular would be issued on the matter based on the recommendation of the Ministry of Health and would ... <a title="Kuwait bans handshakes" class="read-more" href="/kuwait-bans-handshakes/" aria-label="More on Kuwait bans handshakes">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kuwait&#8217;s Ministry of Health has called on mourners gathered at cemeteries to give up handshakes and make eye contact to show their condolences, al-Zarida reported, citing an official.</p>
<p>Saud Al Dabus, director-general of Kuwait Municipality, said a circular would be issued on the matter based on the recommendation of the Ministry of Health and would ban handshakes inside mourning halls.</p>
<p>The ministry said in a circular that the recommendation came out of interest to take preventive measures to protect public health and prevent the spread of communicable diseases due to handshakes.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/kuwait-bans-handshakes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The bad news of the continuation of the cold wave is from the Meteorological Office</title>
		<link>/the-bad-news-of-the-continuation-of-the-cold-wave-is-from-the-meteorological-office/</link>
					<comments>/the-bad-news-of-the-continuation-of-the-cold-wave-is-from-the-meteorological-office/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 21:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10939</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[An extension of the sub-continental high pressure belt is located over West Bengal and adjoining areas. Seasonal normal low pressure is located over South Bay of Bengal. Its extension extends to the northern Bay of Bengal. Therefore, weather over the country may remain dry with partly cloudy sky. However, from midnight to morning, moderate to ... <a title="The bad news of the continuation of the cold wave is from the Meteorological Office" class="read-more" href="/the-bad-news-of-the-continuation-of-the-cold-wave-is-from-the-meteorological-office/" aria-label="More on The bad news of the continuation of the cold wave is from the Meteorological Office">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An extension of the sub-continental high pressure belt is located over West Bengal and adjoining areas. Seasonal normal low pressure is located over South Bay of Bengal. Its extension extends to the northern Bay of Bengal. Therefore, weather over the country may remain dry with partly cloudy sky. However, from midnight to morning, moderate to dense fog may fall in some parts of the country&#8217;s river basins. Again, light to moderate fog may fall in some parts of the country. Therefore, inland waterways may be disrupted due to dense fog.</p>
<p>On the second day, Sunday (January 28) from 6:00 pm onwards, the weather forecast said that the weather will remain dry with temporary partly cloudy skies across the country. From midnight to morning, moderate to dense fog may fall over the river basins of the country. At the same time, the night temperature may increase slightly and the day temperature may remain almost unchanged across the country.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/the-bad-news-of-the-continuation-of-the-cold-wave-is-from-the-meteorological-office/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Saudi allowed marriages in Kaaba Sharif and Masjid an-Nabawi</title>
		<link>/saudi-allowed-marriages-in-kaaba-sharif-and-masjid-an-nabawi/</link>
					<comments>/saudi-allowed-marriages-in-kaaba-sharif-and-masjid-an-nabawi/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 21:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10937</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to the report, the Ministry of Hajj and Umrah of Saudi Arabia has taken this initiative so that marriage can be conducted in the holy Mecca and Medina. Experts say that this is a great opportunity for various institutions to come up with exceptional ideas for organizing weddings there, while preserving the sanctity of ... <a title="Saudi allowed marriages in Kaaba Sharif and Masjid an-Nabawi" class="read-more" href="/saudi-allowed-marriages-in-kaaba-sharif-and-masjid-an-nabawi/" aria-label="More on Saudi allowed marriages in Kaaba Sharif and Masjid an-Nabawi">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to the report, the Ministry of Hajj and Umrah of Saudi Arabia has taken this initiative so that marriage can be conducted in the holy Mecca and Medina.</p>
<p>Experts say that this is a great opportunity for various institutions to come up with exceptional ideas for organizing weddings there, while preserving the sanctity of these two mosques.</p>
<p>A Saudi marriage official named Masoud Al Jabri said that there is religious consent in teaching marriage in mosques. The Holy Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) once taught the marriage of a colleague in the mosque. Many of the local people in Madinah now perform marriage ceremonies in the Masjid al-Nabawi. </p>
<p>He said, Madina residents do this for various reasons. Many people in Medina traditionally invite all their relatives to the wedding. Most of the time the bride&#8217;s family cannot accommodate everyone in the house. As a result, marriage is taught by coming to the Prophet&#8217;s Mosque or the Kaaba. Many believe that it is auspicious if mosque marriage is taught.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/saudi-allowed-marriages-in-kaaba-sharif-and-masjid-an-nabawi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Independent MPs looking at PM</title>
		<link>/independent-mps-looking-at-pm/</link>
					<comments>/independent-mps-looking-at-pm/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 21:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10935</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If that is not possible, the independent parliamentarians want to make the parliament effective by following the directions given by party president Sheikh Hasina about what will be their role in the twelfth National Parliament for the next five years. A handful of Independent MPs were in favor of forming a separate alliance, but most ... <a title="Independent MPs looking at PM" class="read-more" href="/independent-mps-looking-at-pm/" aria-label="More on Independent MPs looking at PM">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If that is not possible, the independent parliamentarians want to make the parliament effective by following the directions given by party president Sheikh Hasina about what will be their role in the twelfth National Parliament for the next five years. A handful of Independent MPs were in favor of forming a separate alliance, but most of the Independent MPs did not agree.</p>
<p>Independent Members of Parliament will sit in a meeting with Awami League President and Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina at Ganabhaban this Sunday evening to take directions on what role they will take in the 12th National Parliament starting from January 30. Independent MPs who won a record number of 62 seats will meet at Ganobhaban at the invitation of the Prime Minister. In today&#8217;s meeting, Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina can give necessary directions regarding the role of individual parliamentarians and reserved seats.<br />
Talking to several independent parliamentarians of Awami League, it is known that they will perform their duties in parliament as per instructions given by party president Sheikh Hasina regarding the role they will play in the national parliament for the next five years. Because, except for a few, all independent members of parliament are directly involved in Awami League politics and hold big positions. Therefore, the newly elected independent members of parliament are looking at the party leader.</p>
<p>Awami League President and Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina will be happy to see them in the role, they will act accordingly. They are unwilling to take any risk of ending their political career by displeasing the party. Rather, independent MPs want to try to ensure their party&#8217;s nomination in the next election by proving their efficiency in the parliament.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/independent-mps-looking-at-pm/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 67/92 objects using Redis
Page Caching using Redis 
Database Caching using Redis

Served from: _ @ 2024-01-27 21:20:59 by W3 Total Cache
-->